

# ANDREW SUN

andrew.s95@outlook.com | (425) 233-9042 | 10700 NE 4th Street, Bellevue, WA 98004

## Summary

Experienced Optimization Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Strong information technology professional that has experience in marketing and database creation as well. Motivated in creating client relationships, contributing to team success, and developing opportunities for the organization. Most recently received two awards in Leadership and Sales Excellence for being a consistent performer month over month and taking initiative in a Team Lead role.

#### Skills

- Search Engine Marketing
- Microsoft Office
- OSX & Windows
- Adobe Creative Cloud Apps

- Relational Databases
- Customer Relationship Management
- Projects & Presentations
- Data Analytics

# Experience

#### SEM Optimization Specialist (Team Lead)

03/2018 - Current

Microsoft (Contract) | Redmond, WA

- Analyzed over 4,000 client accounts and campaigns, in preparation to providing strategic optimization tactics
- Developed plans and feature adoptions in order to help clients improve their ROI/Conversions
- Set up monthly calls to help clients strategize long-term account/campaign plans for growth
- Provided clients with performance insights
- Problem solved/troubleshooting on account and implementation errors

#### **Marketing Intern**

05/2017 - 08/2017

VMRD Inc. | Pullman, WA

- Developed and presented ideas with the Marketing team on projects to improve sales
- Utilized Adobe Creative Cloud to develop advertising/marketing materials
- Managed customer database and company product catalog
- Improved online presence and impressions by working with partnering SEO company

### Microsoft Intern

05/2015 - 08/2015

Microsoft | Beijing, China

- Collaborated with co-interns on projects & presentations
- Utilized data collection via Satellite, Weather, and Pollution sensors to find correlations of trends in polluted areas (Urban Air Team)
- Worked with the Cognitive Services team in utilizing existing APIs to develop functioning applications

# Education and Training

**Bachelor's Degree**: Management Information Systems Washington State University | Pullman, WA

2017